Three AM the cursor blinks alone
새벽 세 시 커서가 홀로 깜빡이네
A thousand functions no one's called
아무도 호출하지 않은 수많은 함수들
The build keeps failing line by line
빌드는 한 줄 한 줄 계속 실패하고
But I keep writing through the wall
하지만 난 벽을 뚫고 계속 써 내려가
Dead code running in the dark
어둠 속을 달리는 죽은 코드
Every class a buried spark
모든 클래스마다 묻혀버린 불꽃
No one downloads no one plays
아무도 다운로드도 플레이도 않네
But the compile light still stays
하지만 컴파일 불빛은 여전히 남아있네
Designed the maps drew every sprite
맵을 디자인하고 모든 스프라이트를 그렸네
Scored the music through the night
밤새도록 음악을 작곡했네
The folder grows the version climbs
폴더는 커지고 버전은 올라가네
A finished game that no one finds
아무도 찾지 못하는 완성된 게임
Dead code running in the dark
어둠 속을 달리는 죽은 코드
Every class a buried spark
모든 클래스마다 묻혀버린 불꽃
No one downloads no one plays
아무도 다운로드도 플레이도 않네
But the compile light still stays
하지만 컴파일 불빛은 여전히 남아있네
Dead code running in the dark
어둠 속을 달리는 죽은 코드
Every class a buried spark
모든 클래스마다 묻혀버린 불꽃
No one downloads no one plays
아무도 다운로드도 플레이도 않네
But the compile light still stays
하지만 컴파일 불빛은 여전히 남아있네